Here they come.
>> [screaming]
>> LET'S SEE IT. LET'S SEE THE SIGN. YEAH.
>> [laughter]
>> IT IS JUNE 17TH of 2026 in exactly 24
hours, the New York Knicks ticker tape
parade will be coming down this street
right here. It's been 56 years since the
New York Knicks had their last ticker
tape parade.
>> [music]
>> Are you putting these signs up for the
parade tomorrow?
>> Yeah, we are.
>> So cool.
>> [music]
>> Looks good.
>> This building here 55 Broadway is taking
pretty extreme precautions for the
parade.
You going to the parade tomorrow?
>> Hell yeah. Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
>> I'm going to be what? I'm excited. I
heard like people going to start getting
here like 6:00 7:00 a.m.
>> That's what I heard, too. The parade
will begin somewhere around here in the
battery. Then it will head north up
Broadway and it will end here in City
Hall.
3:00 p.m. 19 hours until the parade
begins. They appear to be chopping down
some trees [music] so people have a
better view of the parade. The bleacher
seats have been set up. I've already
seen some people taking seats. The
parade doesn't start for 19 hours. You
got your seat?
>> Got my seat. Been here since noon, man.
You know, die hard, bro.
>> Let me see.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Now I'm sitting just across the street
from City Hall where the parade
concludes and the biggest concern here
are these dark storm clouds that have
rolled in the last few [music] hours.
Seen some people with umbrellas.
Casey, let me get a picture with you.
>> What happens if it rains tomorrow?
>> It's still going to happen, baby.
>> happening.
>> Still happening.
>> Baby, it's New York, baby.
>> How does the ticker tape fall if it's
raining?
>> They're going to waterproof it.
>> [laughter]
>> A brief history on the ticker tape
parade. Back in the 1800s, they used a
mechanical stock ticker.
>> [music]
>> This received financial data over
telegraph lines and it printed that data
on ticker tape. Then back in 1886,
during the dedication of the Statue of
Liberty, [music] for some reason, stock
brokers and office workers started
throwing ticker tape out of the windows.
And [music] that's a brief history of
the ticker tape parade.
6:00 p.m., 16 hours until the parade.
They seem to be towing all the cars
along the parade route.
The news is here.
>> I got you.
>> Are you covering the ticker tape parade?
>> Yes, I'm so excited I'm so excited to
see you.
>> What do you think tomorrow morning's
going to be like?
>> Uh mayhem.
>> [music]
>> Am I going to be in a Casey Neistat
video? 7:00 p.m., 15 hours till the
parade.
Sun's back out. Check the weather
report.
Everything seems positive.
Those
Those are all tow trucks.
>> No idea. I thought it may be for the
parade. [music] They're towing every car
on the street south of Canal Street
between the East River and Hudson River,
apparently.
>> 9:00 p.m., came out with the wife and
kids just have a look at things before
the little ones go to bed.
Yo, let's get Casey? Let's go. Let's go.
This is the front of the line, front of
the line. Who's number one? So, you're
going to sleep out here?
>> Yeah.
>> [bell]
>> Look, I didn't want to get up at 3:00 in
the morning. I just know
there are going to be people out there
right now.
4:00 a.m. 6 hours till the parade
starts. A lot of police activity.
All police officers. This is the line to
get in. This is the line at 4:00 in the
morning. I appreciate that. Good luck
today, guys.
I've breached the perimeter. I'm in.
>> Okay, all right. Go ahead.
>> It's okay?
>> [laughter]
>> How you doing?
Nice to see you. Breached the second
perimeter.
Somehow
sort of got permission to run the parade
route.
>> [screaming]
>> How'd you guys get this spot?
>> Get here early.
>> It's almost like some bizarro
alternative universe where the entire
city of New York is only populated by
police officers. It's just swarms of
cops everywhere I go.
>> [music]
>> 5:00 a.m.
5 hours till the parade. I'm on the
Brooklyn Bridge.
It's a little cloudy out, a little
rainy, a little gloomy.
>> [music]
>> 6:00 a.m. 4 hours till the parade.
This is the front line. They're getting
let in here any minute.
>> [music]
>> This is deep as it could possibly be.
Have fun today, guys.
Is it happening? Is it happening?
>> I think it's happening.
>> I think they're going to open the
floodgates.
My prediction, full-on stampede. Think
Lion King.
>> [screaming]
>> This is going to be tricky. I'm
showered, I'm fresh, I'm ready to go,
but I have my boosted board and a
backpack.
And I need to get through security.
Definitely not allowed to do that with
both of those things.
Okay, thank you very much. Sorry for the
trouble, officer. Thank you. Update,
made it through two checkpoints.
They don't like the boosted board.
>> That one.
>> Okay, thank you, officer.
I failed the fourth checkpoint, but the
officer gave me some advice as to how I
can maybe circumvent. What's up?
>> Yo, what's up, brother? Just wait when
you get to like Broadway, you might be
on your own, though.
>> All right, yeah, go on through.
>> Come this way.
>> Skate relaxed. Checkpoint six.
How you doing?
>> Casey.
>> Checkpoint six, not only did he let me
through, he told me I could skate
through.
I can't, I can't barely get through
myself. All right, thanks, guys.
Checkpoint eight, made it through, got
checkpoint nine coming up. I'm going to
get you some medicine for you. Can you
hold him?
>> Casey.
I got a quick pic.
>> [music]
>> Even with the escort, it's so dense in
here.
>> Casey.
>> We are fully stuck.
>> [cheering]
>> Well, I made it.
They want me to jump.
>> [music]
[music]
>> 9:00 a.m.
>> [music]
>> 1 hour left.
>> The crowds outside have asked for one
thing.
Toilet paper.
>> [music]
>> 48 minutes.
[music]
>> Zero hour is here. It is 10:00 a.m. June
18th, 2026.
Here come the Knicks.
>> [cheering]
[singing]
[music]
>> It's madness. It's total madness.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
[music]
[cheering]